(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T20:25:52.296095",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" many times
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's ride!
Ridin' on dreams
Yeah!!
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
To a feeling that I couldn't even imagine
想いになったんだ
It has grown
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost, our
絆が舵になる
Bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We can blow it away
果てしない旅路を今
Now, in the middle of rowing
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
Through this endless journey, there will be difficulties, right?
それも力に変えて
Let's turn that into strength, too
一緒に進むんだよ！
And move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, I can't let it end as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I was able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is a treasure
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In a world of unknown without a map
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!!
Ridin' on dreams
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
Tries to disturb where we're going
あの日誓ったんだ
I swore that day
覚悟は揺るがない
The resolve won't waver
きちんとしないと！って背中
The back that says "You have to do it properly!"
明日への橋になる
Becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしないとね
I have to cherish it more
“あたりまえ”は無いから
Because there is no such thing as "taken for granted"
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that starts from a small boat
どこから始めたらいいか悩んで
Struggling, wondering where to start
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Little by little, we formed a circle and found it
何にも代えられない夢だ
It's a dream that nothing can replace
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the incomplete
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
The feeling is one
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even if it's a slight hope
僕と君でずっと
With you and me, forever
馬鹿にされても
Even if we are made fun of
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, just "thank you" isn't enough
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, I can't let it end as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I was able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is a treasure
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In a world of unknown without a map
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!!
ひとりじゃない
I'm not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
I'll stand up as many times as it takes
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together
願いだって みんなで、さあ！
Even if it's a wish, let's do it together, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!!
Ridin' on dreams
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" many times
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's ride!
Ridin' on dreams
Yeah!!
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
To a feeling that I couldn't even imagine
想いになったんだ
It has grown
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost, our
絆が舵になる
Bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
We can blow it away
果てしない旅路を今
Now, in the middle of rowing
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
Through this endless journey, there will be difficulties, right?
それも力に変えて
Let's turn that into strength, too
一緒に進むんだよ！
And move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, I can't let it end as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine "like myself"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I was able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is a treasure
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In a world of unknown without a map
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!!
Ridin' on dreams
Wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
ひとりじゃない
I'm not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
I'll stand up as many times as it takes
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together
願いだって みんなで、さあ！
Even if it's a wish, let's do it together, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!!
ローソンへお越しの皆さん、
To everyone visiting Lawson,
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
and tell you right now!
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
into feelings I couldn't even imagine
思いになったんだ
they've grown
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost
絆が舵になる
our bonds become the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll just blow it away
果てしない旅路を今
Now, on this endless journey
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there may be hardships along the way
それも力に変えて
turn those into strength as well
一緒に進むんだよ！
and let's move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
夢では終わらせない
won't let it end
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves
“らしく”輝いていたい
wanting to shine "like ourselves"
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
is my treasure
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an unknown world without maps
まだまだ行こう！
let's go even further!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
A sudden wind tries to disturb
行く先乱そうとも
where we're headed
あの日誓ったんだ
but we vowed on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve won't waver
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
A back saying "You gotta do it right!"
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしないとね
We have to cherish it even more
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because there is no "taking it for granted"
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat
どこから始めればいいか迷って
Wondering where we should start
少しずつね 輪になって見つけた
little by little, we formed a circle and found
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream that cannot be replaced by anything
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the unfinished
想いは一つだけ
Our feelings are one
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with just a faint hope
僕と君でずっと
you and me, always
馬鹿にされても
even if we're made fun of
信じたいんだ！
we want to believe!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll always be together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves
“らしく”輝いていたい
wanting to shine "like ourselves"
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an unknown world without maps
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times we stand back up
笑い合っていたい
we want to smile together
願いだって みんなで、さあ！
That's our wish, everyone, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も越えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination
まだまだ行こう！
let's go even further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
and tell you right now!
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's hop aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
into feelings I couldn't even imagine
思いになったんだ
they've grown
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we got lost
絆が舵になる
our bonds become the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll just blow it away
果てしない旅路を今
Now, on this endless journey
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there may be hardships along the way
それも力に変えて
turn those into strength as well
一緒に進むんだよ！
and let's move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here
ねぇ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves
“らしく”輝いていたい
wanting to shine "like ourselves"
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my treasure
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an unknown world without maps
まだまだ行こう！
let's go even further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
急な風が僕らの
A sudden wind tries to disturb
行く先乱そうとも
where we're headed
あの日誓ったんだ
but we vowed on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve won't waver
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
A back saying "You gotta do it right!"
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしないとね
We have to cherish it even more
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because there is no "taking it for granted"
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat
どこから始めればいいか迷って
Wondering where we should start
少しずつね 輪になって見つけた
little by little, we formed a circle and found
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream that cannot be replaced by anything
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the unfinished
想いは一つだけ
Our feelings are one
hololive fes. EXPO26 DAY1 Ridin' on Dreams
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: To all visitors]
Attention For Visitors
hololive Dreams 事前登録受付中！
[hololive Dreams Pre-registration Open!]
角巻わため 大好き！
I love Tsunomaki Watame!
ぺこら
Pekora
天音かなた
Amane Kanata
Pledge of Loyalty
ホロリス各位！声出していけ～！
To all HoloFans! Let your voices be heard!
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
癒月ちょこ
Yuzuki Choco
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
角巻わため
Tsunomaki Watame
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
ベスティア・ゼータ
Vestia Zeta
こぼ・かなえる
Kobo Kanaeru
一伊那尓栖
Ninomae Ina'nis
フワワ・アビスガード
Fuwawa Abyssgard
モココ・アビスガード
Mococo Abyssgard
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ねぇ、君がいたから だよ
Hey, it's because you were there!
ねぇ、ありがとう を 何度も
Hey, thank you so many times over,
今 すぐ に 伝え たい ん だ
I want to tell you right now!
さあ 乗り込もう！
Now let's hop on!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
どんな楽しいこと 描いては
No matter what fun things we picture,
不意に気恥ずかしく 笑ってた
We'd feel a bit shy and laugh about it.
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
Let's look at that future vision's continuation.
手と手繋いで 風も吹き飛ばして
Holding hands, blowing the wind away,
扉を叩いて 連れて行くよ
Knocking on doors and taking you along!
ほら lalalalalala
Look, lalalalalala
聞こえてる 聞こえてる さあ ああ
Can you hear it? Can you hear it? Now, ah...
ハモニー 重ねた言葉 鮮やかな 日々の向こう
Harmonizing layered words, beyond those vibrant days
ずっと君と響く 揺るがぬストーリー
An unshakeable story resonating with you forever
ハモニー 紡いだ夢が 空へ 駆けてゆく
A harmonized, spun dream races up to the sky
煌めき乗せて あなたへ
Carrying its sparkle straight to you
響いて メロディ どこまでも
Resound, melody, go on forever...
何気ないことも出す 一人じゃないよって 深呼吸
Even casual words bring a deep breath—you're not alone
みたいげん楽しむ 魔法の言葉
Magic words to enjoy every experience
一人に気付いて もっと振り返って また君を知って
Realizing I'm not alone, looking back to know you more
そのたびに ちょっと勇気を出して 明日へ取り込んでいって
Each time, finding a little courage to take it into tomorrow
ラララ... 降り積もる 道しるべは まだ
Lalala... The piling up signposts are still...
ラララ... 覚えている 夢のうた
Lalala... Remembering the song of dreams
ハモニー 手を伸ばしたら 足元に 虹がかかる
Harmony: when I reach out my hand, a rainbow forms at my feet
キミと晴れる ステージ
A stage that clears up with you
ハモニー しるした場所へ 運ぶ逆風を 輝き乗せて 世界へ
Harmony: carrying headwinds to the marked place, shining into the world
響いて メロディ いつまでも
Resound, melody, forever and ever...
君と踏み出した あの 一歩 あの瞬間が
That first step and moment I took with you
宝物だって 胸を張る 今
Are treasures I can proudly hold in my heart now
照らして 照らして シャイニー 笑顔でゆくなら 色褪せないまま
Shine on, shine on, shiny! Walking with a smile, never fading
混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Look, our mingling voices...
聞こえてる 聞こえてる うた
Can you hear it? Can you hear the song?
ハモニー 重ねた言葉 鮮やかな 日々の向こう
Harmonizing layered words, beyond those vibrant days
ずっと君と 響く 揺るがぬストーリー
An unshakeable story resonating with you forever
ハモニー 紡いだ夢が 空へ 駆けてゆく
A harmonized, spun dream races up to the sky
煌めき乗せて 世界へ 響いて メロディ
Carrying sparkle into the world, resound, melody!
愛も メロディ どこまでも
Love is also a melody, anywhere...
アレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, time to shine!
呼び合う 声も合図に
With our calling voices as the signal
あれパレ パレ パレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, going to search for it
スタートは 何度だって
No matter how many times we start anew...
独りごと 続いた
Soliloquies kept going on
ただ 始まりだって 走った
But I ran, knowing it was just the beginning
遠い 暗闇に灯った
Lit up in the distant darkness
それは まぶしすぎた 名前
That was a name far too dazzling
それは 切なすぎる 想いで
That was a memory far too bittersweet
もっと 近づけと 手を伸ばした 想いだけ詰めすぎた ほら
Reaching out to get closer, packing in too many feelings—look!
今 迷子は こんなになった
Now this stray child has ended up like this
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, time to shine!
暗闇も 愛しさも すべて置いておいで
Leave all the darkness and affection behind
風に 夢跳ね飛び立てるさ
Riding the wind, dreams can take flight
ささやかなの 今ばかり 終わり
This modest moment is just the end...
涙拭き出し
Wiping away my tears,
君を見つけた顔 胸を張れるよ
I'll proudly show the face that found you.
ここから これから
From here, from now on,
パワフル！パレッパレッパレッ
Powerful! Pa-re-pa-re-pa-re!
頼りない夜更かしを
Unreliable late-night hours,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんかないよ
Let's sing, there's nothing to be embarrassed about!
誰も解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary riddle no one can solve,
いつかまた逢えるよマジナリー
Someday we'll meet again, imaginarily—
あの日 ゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that began from zero on that day.
数えきれないこんなのさ 数えるような思い出じゃないさ
Counting countless things like this—it's not a memory to be counted!
ほら 今 僕らをひとつにしよう
Look, now let's bring us all together as one!
パレッパレッパレッ 美しく咲いたよ
Pa-re, pa-re, pa-re, blooming so beautifully!
許し合える切ない夜は気高く
Nights of forgiving each other's sorrow are noble—
雨 パレッパレッ また来ない空
Rain, pa-re, pa-re, the sky that won't come again.
巡り逢い道、本当は君と歩くことだ
Meeting you, truly, is walking with you—
君と歩くことなんだ
It's walking with you.
ただいまと言えば おかえりって叫ぶよ
When I say "I'm home," shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because it's not something to be taken for granted,
パレッパレッパレッ 輝くんだよ
Pa-re, pa-re, pa-re, it shines bright!
暗闇を満たすのは君と僕だ
What fills the darkness is you and me.
パレッパレッパレッ 輝くんだよ 増やそうもっと愛しさもすべて
Pa-re, pa-re, pa-re, shine bright, let's increase all our affection even more!
風、夢、羽ばたけるさ
Wind, dreams, we can spread our wings!
ささやかな胸ばかり 終わりなき日日し
Just humble hearts, endless days,
君と飛び込んでいく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in with you, what a wonderful start!
ここから これから パワフル パレッパレッ
From here, from now on, powerful! Pa-re-pa-re!
パワフル パレッパレッ
Powerful! Pa-re-pa-re!
さあ皆さん ステージを盛り上がっていきましょう！
Everyone, let's get the stage hyped up!
ステージワン 最初から飛ばしていくぞ！
Stage one, we're going full speed right from the start!
シングルサイズの部屋で一人きり
In a single-sized room, all alone,
思い出すのはあなたとの暮らし
I remember living with you.
物語の舞台は ビルが群れる
The stage of this story is a seaside town
大都会を遠くに見る 海辺の街
where a crowd of buildings can be seen in the distance.
初めて会った日のことだって
I still clearly remember the day we first met.
今でもまだちゃんと覚えている
I still remember it properly.
フォーマルなシャツ ジャケットが少し不似合いなあなた
That formal shirt and jacket didn't quite suit you.
言葉数は少なくて いつも厳しくて
With only a few words, you were always strict,
叱られてばかりで 機械仕掛けの心を
and I was always being scolded. My mechanical heart
無力さが包んでいた
was wrapped in helplessness.
でも あなたを知りたくて 何もかも知っていたくて
But, I wanted to know you. I wanted to know everything about you.
だけど教えてなんて言えず
But I couldn't say "tell me,"
一人 そっと夜に祈る
I silently prayed alone at night.
少しでも分かりたくて そんな日々を繰り返した
I wanted to understand you, even just a little. Those days repeated.
それでも時折見せてくれた 穏やかなあの表情も
Still, sometimes you showed me that gentle expression,
一度だけ浮かべた涙も
and the one time tears appeared,
隠し切れずに溢れていた 優しさだった
overflowing because they couldn't be hidden, that was your kindness.
あの日もそうだった
It was like that that day too.
あれは二人最後の思い出
That was the last memory for both of us.
暗闇でこの手を握り返して笑ってくれた
In the darkness, you held my hand back and smiled at me.
あなたはもういない
You are no longer here.
今でも聴きたくて もう一度聴かせて欲しくて
Even now, I want to listen, I want to hear your voice once more.
優しくて不器用な あなたの声を
Your gentle yet clumsy voice...
厳しい言葉を なんて願う
your strict words. What a wish this is.
Let's go! Everybody, panic!
That's right, I get you now!
Shinbama it's a magic!
絶望を別の未来へ
Zetsubou o betsu no mirai e
Let's go! I take it home!
稍々行く末待つ雨が...
Shōshō yukusue matsutwamesu ga...
This game has only just begun!
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna get, get out!
溢れる欲求導くままに溺れず公認するあたし！
Afureru yokubō michibiku mama ni oborezu ko-nin suru atashi!
Zaku zaku success! I am baddy!
It's a hobby way I make everybody yeah!
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna get, get out!
Stars spark, crowd starts showing all in, I get you lucky tonight!
Get lucky, get out!
思い通りに奇そうは、描いた色夢勝利を… take it home!
Omoimama ni kisouwa, egaita iromu shouri wo... take it home!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together
Lifetime, showtime
Anytime, bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright
(Yeah, the two of us)
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Fuwa! Moco!
(Bau bau bau bau!)
心も体もふわふわで
My heart 'n soul 'n tail are Fuwawa
気持ちごと浮くことあるけど
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
吠えれば魔界の番犬って
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
あなたの笑顔を守りたいよ
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
Fuwa! Moco!
イタズラ好きでロマンチスト
I love being tricky
お散歩大好きルンルン気分はイランぬ？
Doggy kisses are for me
どこでももこもこついていくから
I love lots of walkies
今はまだ吠えたりだけど
Don't need no leashes for me
二人で吠える
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ (Oh!)
I want to be together (Oh!)
Lifetime, showtime
Anytime, bau bau!
Lifetime
Sing with you
Stars wink
Moon spotlight
Furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together
Lifetime, showtime
Anytime, bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright
(Yeah, the two of us)
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Bau! Wooo...
Bau!
昔々檻の中で
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
ワクワクしつつつつ抑えられ婆うふふ
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away
一緒にになっちゃって大変だシュシュエクスプライム
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz we're meant to be free
ゴールを目指して
Make a break for it
足は止まらない笑顔一番
It's playtime! Paws hitting the pavement
お墨付き止まない今はまだまだコワいだけど
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes
二人の絆は強いから絶対壊さない
Gonna keep you smilin'
だからいつだって、いつだって行くデイ
But my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau bau!
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
Lifetime Walk with you!
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
Good times and Bad times It doesn't matter!
We're a pair unbreakable!
いつもいつも一緒だよ Lifetime showtime Everyday! Bau bau!
And that's why Always It's that day! (Today!)
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau bau!
Lifetime Walk with you!
Good times and Bad times It doesn't matter!
いつもいつも一緒だよ
Always It's that day!
Lifetime, showtime Everyday! Bau bau!
Yeah, the two of us Happy, lucky, puppy sisters!
触んないで！ノンノン、どうせっ！いーの！
Don't touch the ears!
触んないで！ノンノン、どうせっ！テイル！
Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ、フワワだよ、バウ！
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! Bau!
フワワじゃないよ、モココだよ、バウ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! Bau!
双子インバウンド魔界の番犬、yeah!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! Bau!
二人で…… ふわもこ！
And together, we're… Fuwamoco!
夢をかけ合わせたら
Gather up our dreams
目が覚めてしまえばの
And suddenly you'll come to realize
無限大になっちゃう
There's as many as there are stars
たくさんあって
Illuminating the night sky
叶えきれない顔だけど
Never-ending dreams
ずっとチャレンジできる
We don't know if they all can be achieved
一緒だから いつのだって 一緒にいたいよ
But we'll keep on going furr-ever Together here with you!
It's showtime I want to be together (Fufu!)
It's showtime I want to be together
ふわふわ、もこもこ包まれて
Fuwa fuwa Moco moco Hand in hand with you
君の笑顔は守りたい 一番の願い
Bring your smile, rain or shine We'll protect it
一生たい 一緒にいたいよ
Won't forget our pledge to you!
Lifetime, showtime Anytime, bau bau!
Lifetime Sing with you
Stars wink Moon spotlight
Furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together.
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright
(Yeah 二人は)
(Yeah, the two of us)
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Fuwa! Moco!
Fuwa! Moco! (Bau bau bau bau!)
My heart n' soul n' tail are Fuwawa
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
Your smile is the treasure I want to keep safe.
Fuwa! Moco!
I love being tricky
Doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies
Don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
Fuwamoco together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
誰がなんと言おうと、今日はクリスマス…
No matter what anyone says, today is Christmas...
これは、キミとの、約束の物語…
This is the story of a promise made with you...
「ペコチキン、いかがぺこ～!?」
"How about some Peko Chicken?!"
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
っしゃいませ らっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さあ さあ 今日も元気に焼いて 焼いて 焼いちゃって
Come on, today too let's grill, grill, grill away!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人 飛んでパーティ様
Lone guests, organizers, single flying party guests!
どうでしょう 一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
えっさ ほいさ 焼き上げろ あっちゅーまに列だ
Heave-ho, bake it up, a queue forms in no time!
レジの向こう お腹 空腹 待たせて sorry
Beyond the register, hungry stomachs, sorry for making you wait!
てんやわんやしちゃう ケド キチントネ 仕上げるゾ
Bustling around, but we'll finish it nicely, zo!
遡る 秘伝のスパイス ラブアンドピース
Tracing back the secret spice, love and peace!
美味しくなれなれ (なれなれ) 歌わせて (歌わせて)
May it be delicious, sing along!
じっくりじっくり こんがりこんがり
Slowly, slowly, nicely browned!
ぎらっと からっと 輝いて
Gleaming, crisp, and shining!
ほかほか シャキーン! 変身だ!
Warm, shing! It's a transformation!
(チキン! チキン! チキン! チキン!)
(Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!)
お待たせ ペコ!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Peko!
噛み食らえ
Devour it!
やめらんねーよ よ やめらんねーよ よ ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ よ とんでもねーよ よ ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
パリッと ジューワッと ホロッと たっぷり アツアツ
Crisp, juicy, tender, plenty of piping hot!
ホラ もう一つ どうでしょう?
Hey, how about one more?
やめらんねーよ な やめらんねーよ な ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ な とんでもねーよ な ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
ガブッと バリッと クラッと にんまり ぺろり
Chomp, crunch, dizzy, grinning, licking lips!
おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
Deliciousness that makes you go crazy!
(オーダー!) いっちょう お届け
(Order!) Delivering one portion!
(オーダー!) ぜったい お届け
(Order!) Definitely delivering!
(チキン! チキン! チキン! チキン!)
(Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!)
お待たせ ペコ!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Peko!
冷めたらチンして ペコチキン
Heat it up in the microwave if it gets cold!
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
っしゃいませ らっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さあ さあ 今日も元気に焼いて 焼いて 焼いちゃって
Come on, today too let's grill, grill, grill away!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人 飛んでパーティ様
Lone guests, organizers, single flying party guests!
どうでしょう 一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
えっさ ほいさ 焼き上げろ あっちゅーまに列だ
Heave-ho, bake it up, a queue forms in no time!
レジの向こう お腹 空腹 待たせて sorry
Beyond the register, hungry stomachs, sorry for making you wait!
てんやわんやしちゃう ケド キチントネ 仕上げるゾ
Bustling around, but we'll finish it nicely, zo!
遡る 秘伝のスパイス ラブアンドピース
Tracing back the secret spice, love and peace!
美味しくなれなれ (なれなれ) 歌わせて (歌わせて)
May it be delicious, sing along!
じっくりじっくり こんがりこんがり
Slowly, slowly, nicely browned!
ぎらっと からっと 輝いて
Gleaming, crisp, and shining!
ほかほか シャキーン! 変身だ!
Warm, shing! It's a transformation!
やめらんねーよ よ やめらんねーよ よ ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ よ とんでもねーよ よ ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
パリッと ジューワッと ホロッと たっぷり アツアツ
Crisp, juicy, tender, plenty of piping hot!
ホラ もう一つ どうでしょう?
Hey, how about one more?
やめらんねーよ な やめらんねーよ な ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ な とんでもねーよ な ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
ガブッと バリッと クラッと にんまり ぺろり
Chomp, crunch, dizzy, grinning, licking lips!
おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
Deliciousness that makes you go crazy!
(オーダー!) いっちょう お届け
(Order!) Delivering one portion!
(オーダー!) ぜったい お届け
(Order!) Definitely delivering!
(チキン! チキン! チキン! チキン!)
(Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!)
お待たせ ペコ!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Peko!
冷めたらチンして ペコチキン
Heat it up in the microwave if it gets cold!
あーあー、この度はご来店いただき、誠に、誠にありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you very much for visiting us today.
本日も元気に焼いておりますのは、肉汁 脳汁 たっぷり! ペコチキンでございます。
Today as well, we're grilling up Peko Chicken, overflowing with juice!
熱く、こんがり、冷やさない。をモットーに
With the motto: Hot, golden brown, never let it cool.
ジューシー バリバリ、ジューシー バリバリ 取り揃えております。
We have juicy and crispy ready for you.
皆様の、日頃のご愛顧に感謝を込めて、ただいまより
With gratitude for your daily patronage, starting right now
チキンフィーバータイム突入とさせていただきます。
we will enter Chicken Fever Time!
それでは、お呼び出しを申し述べます。
Now, we shall call out our customers.
アツアツ チキンのお客さま ＼はーい！／
Customers for piping hot chicken? ＼Yes!／
お一人ぼっちの お客さま ＼はーい！／
Lone customers? ＼Yes!／
自称 パーティ ピープーのお客さま ＼はーい！／
Self-proclaimed party people? ＼Yes!／
骨なし チキンのお客さま ＼はーい！／
Boneless chicken customers? ＼Yes!／
ハニー シロップ ラード ショットのお客さま ＼はーい！／
Honey syrup lard shot customers? ＼Yes!／
ニク アブラ マシマシ カラメのお客さま ＼はーい！／
Extra meat, fat, sauce customers? ＼Yes!／
限界突破 完凸 希望のお客さま ＼はーい！／
Limit broken, maxed out, hopeful customers? ＼Yes!／
お腹 ペコペコ の お客さま ＼はーい！／
Starving hungry customers? ＼Yes!／
(オーダー!) 聖なる夜には?
(Order!) On this holy night?
(チキン! チキン! チキン! チキン!)
(Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!)
どこでも 向かうよ ペコチキン
We'll head anywhere, Peko Chicken!
遅くなって ごめんね
Sorry for being late!
やっと 言えた 世界で
At last, I could say it in this world,
冷えた孤独を 温めたげる
To warm up your cold solitude!
一人じゃないよ もう
You're not alone anymore!
「冷えた食卓に彩りを。それが、聖なるペコチキン!」
"Coloring the cold dining table. That is holy Peko Chicken!"
だから だから
Therefore, therefore,
＼お腹 ペコペコ ペコチキン!／
＼Starving hungry Peko Chicken!／
やめらんねーよ よ やめらんねーよ よ ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ よ とんでもねーよ よ ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
パリッと ジューワッと ホロッと たっぷり アツアツ
Crisp, juicy, tender, plenty of piping hot!
ホラ も一つ どうでしょう?
Hey, how about one more?
冷め ちゃ ヤダ 冷め ちゃ ヤダ ペコチキン
Don't let it get cold, Peko Chicken!
あっためちゃいこ あっためちゃいこ ペコチキン
Let's warm it up, Peko Chicken!
ガブッと バリッと クラッと にんまり ぺろり
Chomp, crunch, dizzy, grinning, licking lips!
おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
Deliciousness that makes you go crazy!
(オーダー!) めっちゃ お届け
(Order!) Delivering a ton!
(オーダー!) すごい お届け
(Order!) Delivering amazingly!
(チキン! チキン! チキン! チキン!)
(Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!)
お待たせ ペコ!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Peko!
今夜は一緒に ペコチキン
Tonight together, Peko Chicken!
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
っしゃいませ らっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さあ さあ 今日も元気に焼いて 焼いて 焼いちゃって
Come on, today too let's grill, grill, grill away!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人 飛んでパーティ様
Lone guests, organizers, single flying party guests!
どうでしょう 一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
えっさ ほいさ 焼き上げろ あっちゅーまに列だ
Heave-ho, bake it up, a queue forms in no time!
レジの向こう お腹 空腹 待たせて sorry
Beyond the register, hungry stomachs, sorry for making you wait!
てんやわんやしちゃう ケド キチントネ 仕上げるゾ
Bustling around, but we'll finish it nicely, zo!
遡る 秘伝のスパイス ラブアンドピース
Tracing back the secret spice, love and peace!
美味しくなれなれ (なれなれ) 歌わせて (歌わせて)
May it be delicious, sing along!
じっくりじっくり こんがりこんがり
Slowly, slowly, nicely browned!
ぎらっと からっと 輝いて
Gleaming, crisp, and shining!
ほかほか シャキーン! 変身だ!
Warm, shing! It's a transformation!
やめらんねーよ よ やめらんねーよ よ ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ よ とんでもねーよ よ ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
パリッと ジューワッと ホロッと たっぷり アツアツ
Crisp, juicy, tender, plenty of piping hot!
ホラ もう一つ どうでしょう?
Hey, how about one more?
やめらんねーよ な やめらんねーよ な ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop, Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ な とんでもねーよ な ペコチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable, Peko Chicken!
ガブッと バリッと クラッと にんまり ぺろり
Chomp, crunch, dizzy, grinning, licking lips!
おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
Deliciousness that makes you go crazy!
(オーダー!) めっちゃ お届け
(Order!) Delivering a ton!
(オーダー!) すごい お届け
(Order!) Delivering amazingly!
(チキン! チキン! チキン! チキン!)
(Chicken! Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!)
お待たせ ペコ!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Peko!
今夜は一緒に ペコチキン
Tonight together, Peko Chicken!
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
っしゃいませ らっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さあ さあ 今日も元気に焼いて 焼いて 焼いちゃって
Come on, today too let's grill, grill, grill away!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人 飛んでパーティ様
Lone guests, organizers, single flying party guests!
どうでしょう 一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
えっさ ほいさ 焼き上げろ あっちゅーまに列だ
Heave-ho, bake it up, a queue forms in no time!
レジの向こう お腹 空腹 待たせて sorry
Beyond the register, hungry stomachs, sorry for making you wait!
てんやわんやしちゃう ケド キチントネ 仕上げるゾ
Bustling around, but we'll finish it nicely, zo!
どうでしょう 一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
バカタレサーカス 参上！
Bakatare Circus, here we come!
行くよー！
Let's go!
Are you ready? For!
上げてけ Foo!!
Raise it up, Foo!!
常識のバカを巻き起こせ！
Stir up a common-sense defying madness!
Are you ready? For!
上げてけ Foo!!
Raise it up, Foo!!
宴の合図 叫びましょう！
Let's shout the signal for the feast!
Yeah!!!!
始まるよ サカダンリ
It's starting, Sakadanri,
思い立ったが ナイスデイ
whenever you feel like it is a nice day.
ナイスデイ！
Nice day!
どこぶらんで ぼっけで るけろん
Dokoburande, debokkede, rukeron,
遊び疲れたら
when we get tired of playing,
暖かなお茶でブレイクタイム
it's break time with warm tea.
弾け飛んで ハリツケて 楽しもう
Let's burst, stick to it, and have fun!
好奇心は止まらない
Our curiosity won't stop,
どんなストーリーが待っているかな
what kind of story is waiting for us?
Are you ready? For!
上げてけ Foo!!
Raise it up, Foo!!
馬鹿なこと起こすお祭りが！
A festival where we cause foolish things!
メイクラン この瞬間を
Make-run, this moment,
バカ騒ぎしよう
let's make a ruckus out of it.
茶々茶でいきなりが 大・事・言・葉 なんていらないよ
Cha-cha-cha, suddenly, important words aren't needed at all.
ワンツーじゃ 果てしなく遠くへ 思いのまま
One-two-jah, endlessly far away, just as we feel.
青春とは切なさだけさ 楽しむしかないじゃん
Youth is only bittersweet, you've got no choice but to enjoy it!
揃いなまま別次元へビューン！
Together into another dimension, zoom!
私たちはベストフレンド！
We are best friends!
一番世界で一番セクシー
The sexiest in the whole world,
止まらないこの機械も
even this unstoppable machine
どうでもねぇ持ってきとんだ
doesn't matter, we brought it along!
ゴーゴー！愛の愛も壊れない！
Go Go! Even love's love won't break!
まだまだコーナーできるよ！行っそー！
We can still corner! Let's go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
Are you ready? For!
上げてけ Foo!!
Raise it up, Foo!!
馬鹿なこと起こすお祭りが！
A festival where we cause foolish things!
ビビッドな3ピース 集まりちゃラヒツ
Vivid 3-piece, gather and rock!
最高潮な時間はほら
The climax time, look,
ギミギミモア！
Gimme gimme more!
のばれずプー！
Nobarezupuu!
皆の先っぽで愛こめて
With love at everyone's tips,
せーの！バカタレサーカス！！
Ready, go! Bakatare Circus!!
好奇心は終わらない
Our curiosity won't end,
どんなストーリーが待っているかな
what kind of story is waiting for us?
大切なこの瞬間を分かち合おう
Let's share this precious moment.
紡いできた思い出もさ
And the memories we've woven,
飾り付けてさあ！
decorate them, come on!
メイクラン
Make-run,
この瞬間をバカ騒ぎしよう
let's make a ruckus out of this moment.
茶々茶でいきなりが
Cha-cha-cha, suddenly,
大事・言葉なんていらないよ
important words aren't needed at all.
ワンツーじゃ！激しく飛んで 思いのまま
One-two-jah! Fly wildly, just as we feel.
青春とは切なさだけさ
Youth is only bittersweet,
楽しむしかないじゃん
you've got no choice but to enjoy it!
がむしゃらがずっとお似合いだ！
Recklessness always suits us best!
私たちはまだはしゃぐよ はっちゃけよう
We're still going to frolic, let's go wild!
ララララ…
La la la...
Yeah!!
みんなありがとー！もっともっと盛り上がってね！
Thank you everyone! Get even more hyped!
最高最高！最高に楽しかった！
Awesome awesome! It was super fun!
ということでちょっとね 皆さん コールアンドレスポンスもしたいと思いますので
So everyone, we'd like to do some call and response,
これもかましちゃいましてね
so let's get into that!
はい 自己紹介タイムやっていきましょうか
Let's do the self-introduction time!
お願いしまーす
Please!
はい 白上フブキ！
Hi, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
皆さん 白上が「コンコンキツネ」って言ったら 「コンコンキツネ」で返してください いけますか？
When I say "Kon-kon kitsune!", please reply with "Kon-kon kitsune!". Ready?
いけまーす
Ready!
皆さん コンコンキツネ！
Everyone, "Kon-kon kitsune!"
コンコンキツネ！
Kon-kon kitsune!
丸もやっとくか
Let's do it again.
ふわふわ尻尾のごぼうて！ 「あなたのお心の 一番ボス！」
"Fluffy tail burdock root!", "The number one boss of your heart!"
白上フブキです ハイタッチ！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki. High five!
ま フェスだからね やっときましょう ジャストでね
Well, it's a fes, so let's do it right on time.
じゃあ あの 私が「はい だーりん」って言ったら 「はい はにー」って返してください
Okay, so when I say "Hi, darling", please reply with "Hi, honey".
あの 「世界で一番」って聞くんで 「愛してる」って返してください
And when I ask "The number one in the world?", please reply with "I love you".
オッケー？
Okay?
できますよー
You can do it!
はい だーりん！
Hi, darling!
はい はにー！
Hi, honey!
世界で一番！
The number one in the world!
愛してるー！
I love you!
ありがとうございます このライブ作詞生しらんいフレアで……
Thank you very much! For this live performance...
みんなわかるよね？
Everyone knows, right?
なんだろ？なんだなんだ？
What is it? What, what?
なんだなんだなんだ？
What, what, what?
ホロライブ４期生
Hololive 4th Generation
角巻ーーきん！ わためえ！
Tsunoma--ki! Watame!
わためえ！
Watame!
違うだろ！
That's not it!
角巻ーーきん！ わためえ！
Tsunoma--ki! Watame!
わためえ！
Watame!
え わためのナンバー１！
Watame is number one!
わためえ！
Watame!
踊りが雑 この始まりなの？
Your dancing was sloppy. Is this how it starts?
だだだだだーん！
Dadadadadarn!
ホロライブ４期生 角巻わためでーす！
I'm Tsunomaki Watame from Hololive 4th Gen!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thank you very much!
でね 思ったんだけどあれじゃないの今ので？
And you know, I thought, wasn't that just now?
わためーのコールはさ「こんばんーーーどぅどぅどぅ」だと思ったじゃん
You'd think Watame's call would be "Konban--doudoudou", right?
あ そうだよ
Ah, that's right.
いつもの挨拶忘れるなよ
Don't forget your usual greeting!
ごめんね！
Sorry!
ということでおまるぽるかのがレスポンスは「ぽるかおるかー」って言ったら「おるよー」って
So for Omaru Polka's call and response, if I say "Polka Olka", you say "Here!".
言ってほしいな
I'd like you to say that.
いくよー！ぽるかおるかー！
Here we go! Polka Olka!
おるよー！
Here!
このライブご機嫌ねぽらぽるの、おまるぽるかです！よろしくお願いしまさーす！
I'm Omaru Polka of Polapol, in high spirits for this live! Nice to meet you!
すごい 揃いだってね いいね いいね！
Amazing, you guys are so in sync. Nice, nice!
どうどうどう？みんな声出てる感じですか？ぽるかさん どうですか？
How is it? Does everyone feel like they're shouting? Polka-san, how was it?
いやね まだ足りないよ 声がちょっとね 確かに！
Well, it's still not enough, voices are a bit... True!
まだイケるよな！
We can still go further!
始まったばっかだもんな！
We just started!
もっとさあ！盛り上げていけよ！
Come on! Let's get more hyped up!
よっしゃ こっちが盛り上がってるか！って聞いて「うおおー！」だの「いぇーい！」なの言ってください！
Alright, when I ask "Are you guys hyped over here?", shout "Woah!" or "Yeah!"!
いくよみんな！ せーの！ 盛り上がってるかー！
Ready everyone? One, two! Are you hyped?!
うおおおー！ いぇーい！
Woah! Yeah!
ありがとう！じゃあ次もやろうよ、メービ。
Thank you! Next, let's do Maby.
あ やろうよ
Ah, let's do it.
メービいっとく？メービ作みつくる？ めちゃめちゃMC時間使うね、我々。
Maby? Should we make Maby? We're spending so much time on MC.
みんなのメービ！
Everyone's Maby!
またあっちかにーじゃこっちから！じゃあこっちからウェーブいきますよ！
From over there to over here! Okay, wave from this side!
ペンライト振って 手もいいよ なんだっていいよ！ 行くよ！ ほんとにさんかぎすっこう！
Wave your pens, hands are fine, anything is fine! Here we go!
おおおおおー！ すっげえ！ すごくよくできました！ ありがとうございます！
Ooh! Amazing! You did really well! Thank you!
ということでね 改めましてセズムスフェス え、ライブ&ドリームズが始まりました。
And so, Sthumus Fes, um, Live & Dreams has begun.
そして今回初の試み皆さん トロッコ見てくれましたかー？
And what's more, for the first time ever, did everyone see the trolleys?
みたー！
We saw them!
すごかったね！
It was amazing!
いやすごかったね！
Yeah, it was amazing!
やっぱ いつもよりね ちょっと我々のことが近くに見えた方々いっぱいいたんじゃないでしょうか？
I bet many of you could see us closer than usual, right?
どうだった？
How was it?
よかった！
It was great!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
またですねえ、えーと帰宅してからでもいいですし、配信見てる方はですね、ぜひともハッシュタグ、ホロライブフェスエスポ２６デイ１で本日感想などなど色々とよろしくお願いします！
And also, you can check after you get home, or if you're watching the stream, please use the hashtag #HololiveFesExpo26Day1 to share your thoughts and impressions!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thank you very much!
そしてなんと え？ え？ え？ え？ え？ え？ え？
And what's more, eh? Eh? Eh?
ああ 早い早い早い早い早い早い！
Ah, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast!
え？
Eh?
4チーム そしてキングダムツアをご覧の 方々はなんと！
The 4 teams and everyone watching the Kingdom Tour, guess what!
ここまで！
This far!
え、まだ見たい？ まだ見たいですよね？
Eh, you want to see more? You still want to see more, right?
まだ見たいよね？
You still want to see more, right?
まだ見たいですよねー！
You still want to see more, right!
ということで皆さん ご覧のとおり まだまだユニット曲は終わってしまったんですけど ソロ曲もありますからね！
So as you can see, the unit songs have ended, but there are solo songs too!
絶対見てね！ねえ！
Be sure to watch! Right!
この言葉を借りて、
If you don't mind borrowing these words...
ま、よければさ、みんなソロ曲の時に、
well, if you like, during everyone's solo songs...
ファンのみんなに何してほしいかっていうのをちょっと、
What should we have fans do?
無理ありますかね？
Are there any requests?
なんかサイリウムの色の、
Like for Cyalume colors—
ペンライトの色、何色がいいとかさ。
Penlight colors, what color is good?
これはオレンジがいい！
This is orange!
オレンジがいい！
Orange!
オレンジ！
え、オレンジ？ え、嘘！？
Orange? No way!
え、でも、なんか、
Well, but...
違うのか。
Does it vary?
曲に合せて、こう手拍子があったら、
Matching the song, with hand gestures...
もっとエモい感じにしてもらったりとかしてほしいな！
Or making it more emotional, or something!
おお、いいですね。
That sounds great!
はーはーはー、はーはー。じゃあ、わためは？
How about Watame?
やっぱ一番デカい声をだしてほしいなと思ってまして。
Well, I want the loudest voice possible!
デカい声出せるよな！
I want you to be able to raise a huge voice!
デカい声！
A huge voice!
デカい声出せるよな！
Let's hear a huge voice!
じゃあ、わためのお願いします。そして、ポルカはどうですか？
So for Watame's solo song, please look forward to it!
もちろん盛り上がってくれるよね？
We'll definitely get you hyped up too, right?
ポルカの時はよろしくお願いします！
For Polka's time, please look forward to it!
あっ、忘れてました。白上ちょっとの、あっ、ペンライトに触れたんですけど、
And Fubuki, Shirakami's solo—
白上のソロ曲の時はぜひとも皆さん、あの、白上のカラーではなくて、皆さんの推しのカラーで、
Shirakami's solo song, please everyone, not Shirakami's color, but everyone's Oshi color!
おおー！ よしよし！
Yes!
もちろんね、推しトムの方は、あの白とか、青でもいいですけども、
Of course, if you have a oshi, white or—
ま、今回のね、あのDAY1含め、ホロライブプロダクションに好きな推しのカラーが皆さんあると思います。
Well, this time, including D1, Hololive Production—
白上のソロ曲の時はぜひとも、皆さんの推しのカラーで、
Shirakami's solo song, please, everyone, with your oshi's color!
振ってくれると、多分すごい綺麗な景色になるんじゃないかと思ってます。
If you wave it, I'm sure it'll make a wonderful view!
なので、白上のソロ曲もお願いします！
Shirakami's solo song, please look forward to it!
さあ、じゃあ配信の、みんなが見てる、なんか、あの羨ましい感じ、みんな、イエーイって、
So, for everyone watching the stream—
ゆったりゆったり配信のみんなに、「イエーイ！」って、
Say it relaxedly to the stream viewers: "Yeah!"
さあじゃあ、続いての楽曲も準備できてるっぽいのでね。
Now then, the following songs are ready too, it seems!
じゃあ行きますか、じゃあ。
Let's go, then!
今回皆さん、「Ridin' on Dreams」がテーマなので、
Now, everyone, "Ridin' on Dreams" is the theme,
これで締めたいと思います。じゃあ行きますよ！せーの！
so let's end with that. Let's go!
Ridin' on Dreams！
Ridin' on Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.